Hello Bonus, welcome.
Today on 17th January, ICICI Lombard General
Insurance Company announced its quarter 3
results. So let's move on to the
consolidated results.
[Music]
Here you can see the consolidated results which are in
rupees in lags. First of all, let's talk about
how much premium the insurance company has collected in this, quarterly and
yearly. If we talk about premium, then
in this quarter the company has taken a premium of Rs. 379 crores, whereas
in the previous quarter a
premium of Rs. 383 crores is visible. We
can consider it as a little growth or flat.
If we talk about the total income of the company, then
in this quarter the
income was Rs. 436 crores, which was Rs.
450 crores in the previous quarter, that is, if
seen quarterly, the income is a little
down. And if seen yearly, the income was Rs. 385
crores in the previous year, which was Rs.
436 crores in this year, out of which Rs.
408 crores have been collected in tax in the year. The
company made a profit of Rs. 35 crores in this current year quarter,
which was Rs.
60 crores in the previous quarter.  The profit was of crores, which means the company suffered a
lot of losses in the quarter, which means the
profit was not good in this quarter.
If you look at the previous year, it was of 31 crores
and this year it is of 35 crores.
Brother, if you talk about its earnings, the earnings for
this quarter is 7.8, which is 7.8 times the earnings of the
previous quarter and
6.47 times the earnings of the previous year, which means yearly the earnings have
fallen a little bit. So, in my
opinion, the results of the company have been a little bad.
If you look at it, then I would
say that you should hold it. It is an
insurance company,
its business will grow a lot in the coming time. So,
if you want to be with it for the long term, then
definitely hold it and
buy it too. If it goes down, that is what I was
saying. Rest you can see the results, it keeps going up and down a
little bit.
In the results, for the long term, the share will always go up.
And how is the business of this company that
its business will do very well in the coming time.
Insurance ICICI in this